- ObjectiveID: 95_s04_01_SearchRing
  Type: SeasonQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 95_s04_01_SearchRing_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9501_Grace_s01_05
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 95_s04_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 95A_Main_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 95_s04_01_SearchRing_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Title"
  Description: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 95_s04_02_GetDaichi
  Type: SeasonQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9501_Grace_s01_05
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 95_s04_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 95_s04_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 95_s04_02_GetDaichi_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Title"
  Description: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 95_s04_03_EnterCastle
  Type: SeasonQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 95_s04_Grace_p01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 95_s04_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 95_s04_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 95_s04_03_EnterCastle_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Title"
  Description: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 95_s04_04_FightMage
  Type: SeasonQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 95_s04_04_FightMage_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9501_Grace_s01_05
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 95_s04_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 95_s04_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 95_s04_04_FightMage_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Title"
  Description: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 95_s04_05_RetrieveRune
  Type: SeasonQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 95_s04_Daichi_p06
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 95_s04_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 95_s04_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Title"
  Description: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Daichi_p06_DefaultDialogue_01"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 95_s04_06_StopDevice
  Type: SeasonQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 95_s04_06_StopDevice_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9501_Grace_s01_05
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 95_s04_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 95_s04_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 95_s04_06_StopDevice_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Title"
  Description: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: 95_s04_07_WrapFrost
  Type: SeasonQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Container
  NpcDestinationId: ""
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 95_s04_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 95_s04_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 95_s04_07_WrapFrost_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Title"
  Description: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Grace_FinishQuest_greet"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: S04_GT_EXPD_01
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: S04_GT_EXPD_01_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 9504_Shailyn_s04_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: s04_GT_EXPD_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 95_s01_X1
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: S04_GT_EXPD_01_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: null
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@S04_GT_EXPD_01_Title"
  Description: "@S04_GT_EXPD_01_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@S04_GT_EXPD_01_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@S04_GT_EXPD_01_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@S04_GT_EXPD_01_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@S04_GT_EXPD_01_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
- ObjectiveID: S04_GT_EXPD_RPT
  Type: Journey
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 61.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_Container
  NpcDestinationId: 95_s04_AoWei
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: ""
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: DarkMatter
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: 1.0
  CanBeAbandoned: "TRUE"
  Title: "@S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_Title"
  Description: "@S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_Desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_StartPrompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_Proposal"
  InProgressResponse: "@S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_Incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@S04_GT_EXPD_RPT_Complete"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: "TRUE"
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
